<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Help on</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/</link><description>Recent content in Help on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Install instructions</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/install-instructions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 13:26:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/install-instructions/</guid><description>MacOS (x86) users MacOS users can simply unzip and run the installer.
For MacOS versions 10.15 and above, you may need to give explicit permission for the installer to run via Settings-&amp;gt;Security-&amp;gt;&amp;ldquo;Open anyway&amp;rdquo;. In rare cases, you may need to use the following command in the terminal for each plug-in:
sudo xattr -d com.apple.quarantine /Library/Audio/Plug-Ins/VST/AmbiBIN.vst ... sudo xattr -d com.apple.quarantine /Library/Audio/Plug-Ins/VST/Spreader.vst ... etc. The installer places the VSTs in the following folder:</description></item><item><title>Download archive</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/download-archive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/download-archive/</guid><description> Old versions of the SPARTA plug-ins are still hosted on the original server, which can be found here. Newer versions are instead hosted on GitHub.</description></item><item><title>Related publications</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/related-publications/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/related-publications/</guid><description>2021 mckenzie2021dataset McKenzie, T., McCormack, L., and Hold, C. 2021, November. Dataset of Spatial Room Impulse Responses in a Variable Acoustics Room for Six Degrees-of-Freedom Rendering and Analysis. arXiv:2111.11882v1 [eess.AS].
This browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.
@misc{mckenzie2021dataset, title={Dataset of Spatial Room Impulse Responses in a Variable Acoustics Room for Six Degrees-of-Freedom Rendering and Analysis}, author={Thomas McKenzie and Leo McCormack and Christoph Hold}, year={2021}, eprint={2111.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/faq/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/faq/</guid><description>Which VST2 hosts do you recommend for these plug-ins? Reaper &amp;gt; MaxMSP = Plogue Bidule &amp;gt; Other.
What does this slider/button/drop-down menu do? The vast majority of sliders, toggle buttons, and drop-down menus have detailed tooltips. Simply hover your mouse over the parameter in question for a few seconds, and the respective tooltip will appear.
Can I use the plug-ins for commercial purposes? All of the plug-ins in the SPARTA suite, COMPASS suite, the HO-SIRR application and the CroPaC-Binaural may be used for commercial purposes.</description></item></channel></rss>