<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Help on</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/</link><description>Recent content in Help on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Update</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/how-to-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 13:26:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/how-to-update/</guid><description>💡
Learn more about semantic versioning and advanced range syntax.
Check for outdated packages The npm outdated command will check the registry to see if any (or, specific) installed packages are currently outdated:
npm outdated [[&amp;lt;@scope&amp;gt;/]&amp;lt;pkg&amp;gt; ...] Update packages The npm update command will update all the packages listed to the latest version (specified by the tag config), respecting semver:
npm update [&amp;lt;pkg&amp;gt;...]</description></item><item><title>Related publications</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/related-publications/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/related-publications/</guid><description>mccormack2020higher McCormack, L., Pulkki, V., Politis, A., Scheuregger, O. and Marschall, M., 2020. Higher-order spatial impulse response rendering: Investigating the perceived effects of spherical order, dedicated diffuse rendering, and frequency resolution. Journal of the Audio Engineering Society, 68(5), pp.338-354.
This browser does not support PDFs. Please download the PDF to view it: Download PDF.
@article{mccormack2020higher, title={Higher-order spatial impulse response rendering: Investigating the perceived effects of spherical order, dedicated diffuse rendering, and frequency resolution}, author={McCormack, Leo and Pulkki, Ville and Politis, Archontis and Scheuregger, Oliver and Marschall, Marton}, journal={Journal of the Audio Engineering Society}, volume={68}, number={5}, pages={338--354}, year={2020}, publisher={Audio Engineering Society} } mccormack2019sparta McCormack, L.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/faq/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/help/faq/</guid><description>Why are there no VST3 versions of the plug-ins? Unfortunately, Steinberg took a step back with the their VST3 SDK regarding multi-channel support
Why are there no AAX versions of the plug-ins? Unfortunately, Avid are not particularly friendly to open-source and free plug-in projects.
Keyboard shortcuts for search? focus: / select: ↓ and ↑ open: Enter close: Esc Other documentation? Netlify Hugo Can I get support? Create a topic:</description></item></channel></rss>