<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The plug-ins on</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/</link><description>Recent content in The plug-ins on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overview</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/overview/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/overview/</guid><description>The SPARTA installer also includes the COMPASS suite, the HO-DirAC suite, CroPaC Binaural Decoder, and the HO-SIRR room impulse response renderer. These plug-ins employ parametric processing and are signal-dependent. They aim to go beyond conventional linear Ambisonics algorithms, used by the baseline SPARTA plug-ins, by extracting meaningful parameters over time and subsequently employing them to map the input to the output in a more informed manner.
All included plug-ins SPARTA plug-ins More detailed descriptions can be found in SPARTA Suite →</description></item><item><title>SPARTA suite</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/sparta-suite/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/sparta-suite/</guid><description>Plug-in descriptions All plug-ins are tested using REAPER (64-bit), which is a very affordable and flexible DAW and is currently the only recommended host for these plug-ins; although, other hosts are also known to work. Currently, the plug-ins support sampling rates of 44.1 or 48kHz. All spherical harmonic-related plug-ins conform to the Ambisonic Channel Number (ACN) ordering convention and offer support for both orthonormalised (N3D) and semi-normalised (SN3D) normalisation schemes; note that the AmbiX format uses ACN/SN3D.</description></item><item><title>COMPASS suite</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/compass-suite/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/compass-suite/</guid><description>Plug-in descriptions COMPASS VSTs is a collection of flexible VST audio plug-ins for spatial audio production, manipulation, and reproduction, developed by Dr. Archontis Politis, Leo McCormack and Dr. Sakari Tervo in the Acoustics Lab at Aalto University.
COMPASS is a framework for parametric spatial audio processing of sound scenes captured in the Ambisonics format. Parametric methods, such as Directional Audio Coding (DirAC) or HARPEX have gained notoriety recently for being able to achieve sharpness or envelopment beyond first or lower-order traditional Ambisonics playback, using the same lower-order Ambisonics signals.</description></item><item><title>HO-DirAC suite</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/hodirac-suite/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/hodirac-suite/</guid><description>Plug-in descriptions Directional Audio Coding (DirAC) has been an active research topic at Aalto University since 2007 [1]. The method operates by estimating spatial parameters to describe the input sound scene over time and frequency, which are then used to conduct the mapping of the input Ambisonic signals to the output loudspeaker/binaural channels in an adaptive and informed manner. While the original intention of DirAC was for low bitrate compression and transmission of Ambisonic recordings, more recent years have instead focussed on using it for the enhancement of Ambisonics reproduction.</description></item><item><title>HO-SIRR</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/hosirr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/hosirr/</guid><description>Application description Higher-order Spatial Impulse Response Rendering (HO-SIRR) is a rendering method, which can synthesise output loudspeaker array room impulse responses (RIRs) using input spherical harmonic (Ambisonic/B-Format) RIRs of arbitrary order [1,2]. The method makes assumptions regarding the composition of the sound-field and extracts spatial parameters over time, which allows it to map the input to the output in an adaptive and more informed manner; when compared to purely linear methods such as Ambisonics.</description></item><item><title>CroPaC-Binaural</title><link>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/cropac-binaural/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://leomccormack.github.io/sparta-site/docs/plugins/cropac-binaural/</guid><description>Paper abstract Binaural ambisonics decoding is a means of reproducing a captured or synthesised sound-field, as described by a spherical harmonic representation, over headphones. The majority of ambisonic decoders proposed to date are based on a signal-independent approach; operating via a linear mapping between the input spherical harmonic signals and the output binaural signals. While this approach is computationally efficient, an impractically high input order is often required to deliver a sufficiently accurate rendition of the original spatial cues to the listener.</description></item></channel></rss>